[electronic beeping]
[crowd cheering]
[epic music playing]
[music continues in background]
[in Japanese] Perfect, Hiro.
Let's get out once the actress
ahead of us is past the main photo line.
[Hiro] Who is that?
[woman chuckles] You don't know her?
That's Do Ra-mi.
The one who's blowing up globally.
Do Ra-mi.
No, I don't know her.
You really don't?
You haven't seen the Do Ra-mi movie?
-[Hiro inhales sharply]
-He has.
It was in your Netflix viewing history,
both this month and last.
Right, that killer zombie?
What was the actress's name again?
Cha Mu-hee.
Her name was in your search history,
yet you don't remember?
Why do you even have my tablet?
You said to always stand by
with it in hand.
Don't snoop without permission.
-Mirror.
-[woman] Here.
[Hiro humming]
Okay.
[breathes deeply]
What's up with her?
Why's she standing there like a zombie?
You're right, she is.
She's been standing there long enough.
What is she doing?
She should go so you can have your moment.
Something seems off with her.
She doesn't look well.
If she faints, this red-carpet event
will come to a screeching halt.
But I waited three months.
I waited three months
for this custom-made suit from Italy.
I can't let that happen.
-Hiro!
[woman] No way.
Is he going to walk past her?
He wouldn't do something so insane,
even if he wants to show off
that custom-made suit.
[presenter] Hiro is attending
the Tokyo International Film Festival
for the second year in a row.
This year, his performance as Hideo
in Can I Love You? earned him acclaim.
[upbeat pop music playing]
[crowd cheering]
Wake up.
I'll help you.